Thank you for watching!
Yes, I'd like to talk about the clothes I wore this time.
I wanted to use a lot of white.
This white T-shirt and the way it's stroked.
I thought it would be better to wear something with a little volume on the shoulders.
I'm not sure how to say it,
I'd like to wear something that has volume on the shoulders.
I like to wear something with volume on the shoulders.
I also like jumperskirts, but
I like jumperskirts, but I've never seen a seasil-type skirt like this.
I chose this one and matched it with purple check pants.
What do you think?
The point is that the total price of the outfit, including shoes and bracelets, was about 7,000 yen (about 8,000 yen, maybe).
It might have been around 8,000 yen.
That's right. So, I made the clothes easy to imitate for both men and women.
I am waiting to see how many people will wear the same clothes at the benefit.
Yes, I am sure that both men and women will be able to pull it off,
How scary!
Also, I tried on a shirt for the first time.
I've never worn a shirt with this kind of pattern before, even though I have one,
This is my first time wearing one.
Yes, what is the point of coordination?
I tend to wear long sleeves in summer.
I wore the shirt with a punk top.
I thought it would be brighter if I wore beige tomorrow.
I decided to wear white beige.
I decided to wear silver accessories.
I brought black socks, but I happened to find a pair of Billerys socks at the site.
But I happened to find a pair of Billerise socks at the site.
So I matched them with the socks.
Hi, I'm Yuko Sakura.
What is the point of this outfit?
I knew it!
This short shirt
but...
It's called a "mise-en-scène bra".
The logo is intentionally left out.
so that you can see it properly.
I bought this short shirt for the first time
I bought it for the first time.
No, no, no.
I usually wear long shirts.
I usually wear them when I do some kind of uniform cosplay.
I thought I could use it
I thought I could make use of it.
Yes.
It's really easy to use, and the panties sticking out of the pants.
The panties are actually the same logo, so it's like they're matching, and they're showing, and there's a little bit of a waistband.
I wore loose-fitting pants to give it a more modest look this time.
I've never really done a mode look before. I've done cool, cute, and sexy styles.
I've done cool, cute, and sexy types before, but I've never really had a "mode" look, so I asked the makeup artist to give me a "mode" look.
That's all.
Yes, I was told that this was the best coordinate.
I was told it was the best coordinate, but I still don't understand what it's all about.
This is Anemal 2 on the bottom.
This is Anemal 1.
Oh, it's the other way around.
And this is Anemal 2.
I borrowed these.
I bought this one and this one at ZozTown.
Two of these.
I wonder what they are...
Sporty
sporty
It has a Korean look to it
Sporty-like
sporty
I wanted to wear a sporty look because I wanted to show my legs in a summery way, and I wanted him to look like that.
And the bangs.
I wanted to make him look like that.
And he had bangs.
me
This time, I'd like to point out this dress!
The price has been reduced from the original price to 2,000 yen!
We are good at coordinating inexpensive items.
I'm good at coordinating inexpensively, so I've made sure that everything is in the 2000 yen range.
I even collected accessories for the whole body!
I also changed my hair style, so it looks totally different from my usual style.
I dare to say it's a personal coordinate, but I chose clothes that are not personal at all.
What do you think?
The other thing is that it will be sold in the summer.
Since the best coordinate is really to shoot in plain clothes
I chose what I usually wear.
Yes, I do.
I sweat easily.
So I wanted something breathable
something breathable.
Also, you know...
I often wear it in summer.
Yes.
This time, since it was a summer coordinate
I put a lot of blue in the skirt.
And on top of that
Well...
How should I put it?
I wanted to create a loose look.
I added silver in various places
I put silver in various places to balance it out.
Yay!
Yes, the point of the outfit is...
I've been into mature fashion lately.
I've been into mature fashion since last year.
I've been into mature fashion since last year, so I decided to go for a mature look this time, too.
It's cute!
She said it doesn't look like a one-piece outfit.
"It doesn't look like a one-piece outfit.
I'm glad.
Thank you for watching!
I think the key point of this dress is the ribbon on this blouse.
The ribbon can be made to be tightened here.
You can adjust the openness of the ribbon by squeezing it and making it snug here as well,
I also bought a lot of ribbons to go with it,
I also bought a lot of ribbons and put them on my head to make this too dolly coordinate fit in.
To myself.
When I first took it off, I wondered if it would be okay for me,
I wondered if it would be okay for me as a casual wear,
But then I heard about it,
Surprisingly, it worked when I tried it on.
It's too girly.
The theme of the event.